cgtextures.com 2019-07-03

# Textures for 3D, graphic design and Photoshop!

Through its online service, www.textures.com will process privacy-sensitive or personal data. Textures.com values the privacy of its customers and observes due care in processing and protecting personal data. We process data in compliance with the requirements laid down by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act (DPDA). Textures.com is the party responsible for all data processing. Since our data processing falls within the scope of the statutory exemption, it is not registered with the Dutch Data Protection Authority. In this privacy statement, we will explain which personal data we collect and for which purposes. We recommend that you read it carefully. This privacy statement was last amended on 26 September, 2014.

Use of Personal Data

By using our service, you are providing certain data to us. This could be personal data. We only retain and use the personal data provided directly by you or for which it is clear that it has been supplied to us to be processed. As soon as your personal data is no longer necessary to process our online services, your data will be deleted. If storage of data is necessary for legal reasons, it will be stored and blocked for any other use.

Registration

Certain features of our service require you to register beforehand. After your registration we will retain your email address and the personal data you provided. We will retain this data so that you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our website, invoicing and payment, and to provide an overview of the products and services you have purchased from us. We will not provide this to third parties, unless it is necessary for the execution of the agreement you concluded with us or if this is required by law. In the event of suspicion of fraud or misuse of our website we may hand over personal data to the entitled authorities. To register on our website we require your name and email address.

Premium Membership

Through www.textures.com, you can take out a paid Membership. For this we require the following data:

Name

Email Address

Address

Company name

EU VAT Number (only for companies in the European Union)

Advertisements

Our service displays advertisements by Google Adsense, for information on data collection by Google please visit the [Google Privacy Policy page](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

Providing Data to Third Parties

Your data is not provided to third parties.

Security

We take security measures to prevent misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. We keep statistics on our website, giving us access to individual data. However, we only access individual data insofar as necessary for the purposes set out in this statement.

Third-party websites

This statement is not applicable to third-party websites connected to this website through links or banners. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data in a secure and careful manner. We recommend you read these websites privacy statements before making use of these websites.

Cookies

We make use of cookies on our website. A cookie is a small file containing pages of this website. These cookies are send to the hard drive of your computer by your browser. The information stored in the cookies can be returned to our servers or those of the relevant third parties if you decide to visit our website again. Google Analytics, Adsense and DoubleClick Through our website, cookies are placed from the U.S. company Google, as part of the ‘’Analytics’’, ‘’Adsense’’ and ‘’DoubleClick’’ services. Textures.com uses Google Analytics, which is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Textures.com uses the information to examine the website’s usage and prepare reports on the website’s activities. Textures.com uses the DoubleClick and Adsense services to help us provide online advertising management and advertising serving solutions. Google may supply this information to third parties if Google is legally required to, or if third parties process the information on Google's behalf. We do not have any influence on the use of the data by Google and / or a third party. We advise you to read the privacy policy of Google (which may change frequently) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process trough cookies. The information we collect is anonymous as much as possible. The information is transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google does adhere to the Safe Harbor principles and is affiliated to the Safe Harbor program of the U.S. Department of Commerce. This means that there is an adequate level of protection for the processing of personal data, if any. More information about the use of cookies can be found in the instructions and / or by using the Help function of your browser.

Changes to this Privacy- Cookie statement

We reserve the right to modify this statement. We recommend that you review this statement regularly, so that you remain informed of any changes. Right to access and correct or delete your information You have the right to ask for access to and correction or deletion of your personal data. See our contact page. To prevent abuse, we ask you to adequately identify yourself. When it comes to access personal information associated with a cookie, you must include a copy of the cookie. You can find them in your browser settings.

Contact

Textures.com  
Beukelaarsstraat 72B  
3074HG Rotterdam  
The Netherlands

Email: [support@textures.com](mailto:%20support@textures.com)  
Chamber of Commerce registration number: 24422008  
EU VAT number: NL144155874B01
